Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-120 (1969: June 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-121 (1969: June 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-122 (1969: June 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-123 (1969: June 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-124 (1969: June 27)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-125 (1969: June 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-126 (1969: July 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-127 (1969: July 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-128 (1969: July 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-129 (1969: July 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-130 (1969: July 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-131 (1969: July 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-132 (1969: July 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-133 (1969: July 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-134 (1969: July 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-135 (1969: July 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-136 (1969: July 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-137 (1969: July 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-138 (1969: July 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-139 (1969: July 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-140 (1969: July 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-141 (1969: July 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-142 (1969: July 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-143 (1969: July 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-144 (1969: July 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-145 (1969: July 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-146 (1969: July 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.69-146 (1969: July 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-146 (1969: Aug. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-147 (1969: Aug. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-148 (1969: Aug. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-149 (1969: Aug. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-150 (1969: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-151 (1969: Aug. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-152 (1969: Aug. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-153 (1969: Aug. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-154 (1969: Aug. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-155 (1969: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-156 (1969: Aug. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-157 (1969: Aug. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-158 (1969: Aug. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-159 (1969: Aug. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-160 (1969: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-161 (1969: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-162 (1969: Aug. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-163 (1969: Aug. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-164 (1969: Aug. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-165 (1969: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: no.69-166 (1969: Aug. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-167 (1969: Sep. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-168 (1969: Sep. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-169 (1969: Sep. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-170 (1969: Sep. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-171 (1969: Sep. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-172 (1969: Sep. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-173 (1969: Sep. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-174 (1969: Sep. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-175 (1969: Sep. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-176 (1969: Sep. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-177 (1969: Sep. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-178 (1969: Sep. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-179 (1969: Sep. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-180 (1969: Sep. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-181 (1969: Sep. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-182 (1969: Sep. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-183 (1969: Sep. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-184 (1969: Sep. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-185 (1969: Sep. 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-186 (1969: Sep. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Notes: no.69-187 (1969: Sep. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-188 (1969: Oct. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-189 (1969: Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-190 (1969: Oct. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-191 (1969: Oct. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-192 (1969: Oct. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-193 (1969: Oct. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-194 (1969: Oct. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-195 (1969: Oct. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-196 (1969: Oct. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-197 (1969: Oct. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-198 (1969: Oct. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-199 (1969: Oct. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-200 (1969: Oct. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-201 (1969: Oct. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-202 (1969: Oct. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-203 (1969: Oct. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-204 (1969: Oct. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-205 (1969: Oct. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-206 (1969: Oct. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-207 (1969: Oct. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-208 (1969: Oct. 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.69-209 (1969: Oct. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-210 (1969: Nov. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-211 (1969: Nov. 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-212 (1969: Nov. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-213 (1969: Nov. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-214 (1969: Nov. 10)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-215 (1969: Nov. 12)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-216 (1969: Nov. 13)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-217 (1969: Nov. 14)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-218 (1969: Nov. 17)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-219 (1969: Nov. 18)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-220 (1969: Nov. 19)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-221 (1969: Nov. 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-222 (1969: Nov. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-223 (1969: Nov. 24)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-224 (1969: Nov. 25)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-225 (1969: Nov. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: no.69-226 (1969: Nov. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-227 (1969: Dec. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-228 (1969: Dec. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-229 (1969: Dec. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-230 (1969: Dec. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-231 (1969: Dec. 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-232 (1969: Dec. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-233 (1969: Dec. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-234 (1969: Dec. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-235 (1969: Dec. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-235 (1969: Dec. 12)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-236 (1969: Dec. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-237 (1969: Dec. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-238 (1969: Dec. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-239 (1969: Dec. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-240 (1969: Dec. 19)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-241 (1969: Dec. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-242 (1969: Dec. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-242 (1969: Dec. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-243 (1969: Dec. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-244 (1969: Dec. 30)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: no.69-245 (1969: Dec. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-1 (1970: Jan. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-2 (1970: Jan. 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-3 (1970: Jan. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-4 (1970: Jan. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-5 (1970: Jan. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-6 (1970: Jan. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-7 (1970: Jan. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-8 (1970: Jan. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-9 (1970: Jan. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-10 (1970: Jan. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-11 (1970: Jan. 19)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-12 (1970: Jan. 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-13 (1970: Jan. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-14 (1970: Jan. 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-15 (1970: Jan. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-16 (1970: Jan. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-17 (1970: Jan. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-18 (1970: Jan. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-19 (1970: Jan. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: no.70-20 (1970: Jan. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-21 (1970: Feb. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-22 (1970: Feb. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-23 (1970: Feb. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-24 (1970: Feb. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-25 (1970: Feb. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-26 (1970: Feb. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-27 (1970: Feb. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-28 (1970: Feb. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-29 (1970: Feb. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-30 (1970: Feb. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-31 (1970: Feb. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-32 (1970: Feb. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-33 (1970: Feb. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-34 (1970: Feb. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-35 (1970: Feb. 24)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-36 (1970: Feb. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-37 (1970: Feb. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: no.70-38 (1970: Feb. 27)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-39 (1970: Mar. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-40 (1970: Mar. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-41 (1970: Mar. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-42 (1970: Mar. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-43 (1970: Mar. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-44 (1970: Mar. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-45 (1970: Mar. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-46 (1970: Mar. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-47 (1970: Mar. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-48 (1970: Mar. 13)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-49 (1970: Mar. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-50 (1970: Mar. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-51 (1970: Mar. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-52 (1970: Mar. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-53 (1970: Mar. 20)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-54 (1970: Mar. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-55 (1970: Mar. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-56 (1970: Mar. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-57 (1970: Mar. 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-58 (1970: Mar. 27)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-59 (1970: Mar. 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: no.70-60 (1970: Mar. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-61 (1970: Apr. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-62 (1970: Apr. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-63 (1970: Apr. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-64 (1970: Apr. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-65 (1970: Apr. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-66 (1970: Apr. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-67 (1970: Apr. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-68 (1970: Apr. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-69 (1970: Apr. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-70 (1970: Apr. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-71 (1970: Apr. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-72 (1970: Apr. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-73 (1970: Apr. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-74 (1970: Apr. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-75 (1970: Apr. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-76 (1970: Apr. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-77 (1970: Apr. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-78 (1970: Apr. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-79 (1970: Apr. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-80 (1970: Apr. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-81 (1970: Apr. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: no.70-82 (1970: Apr. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-83 (1970: May 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-84 (1970: May 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-85 (1970: May 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-86 (1970: May 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-87 (1970: May 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-88 (1970: May 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-89 (1970: May 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-90 (1970: May 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-91 (1970: May 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-92 (1970: May 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-93 (1970: May 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-94 (1970: May 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-95 (1970: May 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-96 (1970: May 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-97 (1970: May 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-98 (1970: May 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-99 (1970: May 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-100 (1970: May 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-101 (1970: May 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: no.70-102 (1970: May 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-104 (1970: June 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-105 (1970: June 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-106 (1970: June 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-107 (1970: June 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-108 (1970: June 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-109 (1970: June 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-110 (1970: June 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-111 (1970: June 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-112 (1970: June 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-113 (1970: June 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-114 (1970: June 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-115 (1970: June 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-116 (1970: June 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-117 (1970: June 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-117 (1970: June 22)